WE'VE GOT THREE MINUTES
TILL THE REACTOR BLOWS.
WE'RE NEVER
GOING TO MAKE IT.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET
OUT OF HERE!
SAVE YOURSELF.
NO, I WON'T LEAVE YOU.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I'M A ROBOT.
I'M JUST A MACHINE!
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
NOT TO ME.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT?
I AM EXTREMELY TALENTED.
YEAH, YEAH, YOU'RE GREAT.
OKAY, LET'S TAKE IT FROM...
NO, I MEAN I WAS REALLY
ACTING MY ASS OFF.
WELL, I THOUGHT
I WAS PRETTY GOOD, TOO.
OH, YEAH, YOU'RE SOLID.
YOU'RE JUST NO... ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I THINK
THAT'S ENOUGH FOR NOW.
I DON'T WANT TO BE
OVER-REHEARSED.
FINE! I'LL DO IT WITHOUT YOU!
I DON'T NEED YOU
OR ANYBODY ELSE!
I'M GOING TO MAKE IT
ON MY OWN!
YOU'LL SEE!
YOU'LL ALL SEE!
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
SO, WHAT'S THIS THING
YOU'RE AUDITIONING FOR?
OH, IT'S A NEW TV SHOW.
I'M UP FOR THE PART
OF MAC MACKAVELLI...
OR "MAC."
REALLY?
YEAH.
I'M A DETECTIVE
AND I SOLVE CRIMES
WITH THE HELP
OF MY ROBOT PARTNER.
HE'S A COMPUTERIZED HUMANOID
ELECTRONICALLY ENHANCED
SECRET ENFORCER.
OR "CHEESE."
SO, MAC AND CHEESE.
THAT'S THE TITLE.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THEY REALLY LUCKED OUT
THAT THE INITIALS SPELL
"CHEESE."
THAT IS LUCKY.
HUH.
SO, JOEY,
IF YOU GET THIS
YOU'RE GOING TO BE, LIKE,
THE STAR OF YOUR OWN TV SHOW.
I MEAN, YOU'LL BE
LIKE THE BIG CHEESE.
OR THE BIG MAC.
HEY, YOU LOVE THOSE.
WELL, DON'T GET
YOUR HOPES UP
BECAUSE IT'S PROBABLY
NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
NOW, NOW, WHY WOULD
YOU SAY THAT, JOSEPH?
COME ON,
YOU GUYS.
MY OWN TV SHOW?
I JUST... I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M GOOD ENOUGH.
I AM.
Rachel:
WELL, JOEY
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU'RE A TERRIFIC ACTOR.
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
HOW CAN YOU EVEN
ASK THAT QUESTION?
WHOA,
SHE'S PRETTY.
YEAH.
OH, AND SHE'S REALLY NICE, TOO.
SHE TAUGHT ME ALL ABOUT,
YOU KNOW
HOW TO WORK WITH THE CAMERAS
AND "SMELL THE FART" ACTING.
HUH.
I'M SORRY...
WHAT?
EXCUSE ME?
IT'S LIKE, YOU
GOT SO MANY LINES
TO LEARN SO FAST
THAT SOMETIMES
YOU NEED A MINUTE
TO REMEMBER
YOUR NEXT ONE.
SO, WHILE YOU'RE
THINKING OF IT
YOU TAKE THIS BIG PAUSE,
WHERE YOU LOOK ALL INTENSE
YOU KNOW, LIKE THIS.
OKAY.
MMM.
OH.
( rattling )
OH, HERE'S MY SCENE!
HERE'S MY SCENE!
Mrs. Wallace?
I'm Dr. Drake Ramoray
your sister's neurosurgeon.
Your sister is suffering
from a...
( with heavy accent ):
YEAH, EVA...
WE'VE DONE SOME
EXCELLENT WORK HERE
AND I WOULD HAVE TO SAY
YOUR PROBLEM IS QUITE CLEAR.
( piano plays )
♪ ALL YOU WANT IS A DINKLE ♪
♪ WHAT YOU ENVY IS A SCHWANG ♪
♪ WHAT THING THROUGH WHICH
YOU CAN TINKLE ♪
♪ OR PLAY WITH
OR SIMPLY LET HANG. ♪
I PLAY AL PACINO'S BUTT.
ALL RIGHT?
HE GOES INTO THE SHOWER
AND THEN I'M HIS BUTT.
OH, MY GOD.
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
THIS IS A REAL MOVIE,
AND AL PACINO'S IN IT
AND THAT'S BIG.
OH, NO, IT'S TERRIFIC.
YOU DESERVE THIS.
AFTER ALL YOUR YEARS
OF STRUGGLING, YOU'VE FINALLY
BEEN ABLE TO CRACK
YOUR WAY INTO
SHOW BUSINESS.
OKAY, FINE. MAKE JOKES.
I DON'T CARE.
THIS IS A BIG BREAK FOR ME.
YOU'RE RIGHT. IT IS.
SO, YOU GOING TO INVITE
US ALL TO THE BIG OPENING?
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
I'M OUT OF HERE.
WISH ME LUCK.
♪ GOOD LUCK, GOOD LUCK ♪
♪ WE ALL WISH YOU GOOD LUCK. ♪
YEAH, WHATEVER.
IT'S YOUR TURN.
OH, ARE WE PLAYING THIS?
HEY.
HEY. HOW'D THE
AUDITION GO?
TERRIBLE.
I MESSED UP EVERY LINE.
I SHOULDN'T EVEN
BE AN ACTOR.
WAIT A MINUTE.
ARE YOU DOING THAT THING
WHERE YOU PRETEND
IT DIDN'T GO WELL
BUT IT REALLY
DID GO WELL?
YEAH. DID I FOOL YOU?
TOTALLY.
SO IT DID GO WELL.
IT WENT AMAZINGLY WELL.
THAT'S GREAT.
GREAT.
YEAH. IT'S DOWN TO ME
AND TWO OTHER GUYS.
I KNOW BOTH OF THEM
AND THEY'RE REALLY GOOD.
ONE OF THEM IS THE GUY
FROM THOSE ALLERGY COMMERCIALS
WHO'S ALWAYS GETTING CHASED
BY THOSE BIG FLOWERS.
OH, I LOVE THAT GUY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT AM I DOING?
I'M SO NERVOUS, YOU KNOW.
THE CALLBACK ISN'T UNTIL
TOMORROW AT 5:00.
I FEEL LIKE MY HEAD'S
GOING TO EXPLODE.
WELL, IT IS OVERDUE.
LOOK, DON'T WORRY, OKAY?
YOU'RE GOING
TO BE FINE.
THERE'S JUST SO MUCH PRESSURE.
NO OFFENSE, BUT WHAT YOU GUYS
ALL DO IS VERY DIFFERENT.
I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
YEAH, NONE OF
THE REST OF US
HAVE TO DEAL WITH
PRESSURE AT OUR JOBS.
YES, FRAN, I KNOW
WHAT TIME IT IS
BUT I'M LOOKING AT THE WEENUS
AND I'M NOT HAPPY.
WELL, I'M TEARING
THE LETTUCE.
UH-HUH. IS IT DIRTY?
NO, DON'T WORRY,
I'M GOING TO WASH IT.
DON'T. I LIKE IT DIRTY.
THAT'S YOUR CALL.
SO, UH... WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO NEXT?
WELL, I THOUGHT THAT
I WOULD CUT UP THE TOMATOES.
ARE THEY, UH, FIRM?
THEY'RE ALL RIGHT.
YOU SURE
THEY HAVEN'T GONE BAD?
YOU SURE THEY'RE NOT
VERY, VERY BAD?
NO, REALLY, THEY'RE OKAY.
YOU GOING TO SLICE THEM UP
REAL NICE?
ACTUALLY, I WAS GOING
TO DO THEM JULIENNE.
( moaning )
I'M OUT OF HERE.
MONICA, I'M QUITTING.
I JUST HELPED AN 81-YEAR-OLD
WOMAN PUT ON A THONG
AND SHE DIDN'T EVEN BUY IT.
I'M TELLING YOU, I'M QUITTING.
THAT'S IT. I'M TALKING
TO MY BOSS RIGHT NOW.
YES, I AM.
YES, I AM. YES, I AM.
OKAY, BYE. CALL ME
WHEN YOU GET THIS MESSAGE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, HE CAME IN
FOR A MASSAGE...
AND EVERYTHING
WAS FINE UNTIL...
OH...
OH, MY GOD.
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN, HIS HANDS
WEREN'T THE PROBLEM ANYMORE.
WAS IT...
OH, BOY SCOUTS COULD
HAVE CAMPED UNDER THERE.
YOU ATE MY SANDWICH?
IT WAS A SIMPLE MISTAKE.
IT COULD HAPPEN TO ANYONE.
OH, REAL-REALLY?
NOW, NOW, CALM DOWN.
COME LOOK IN MY OFFICE.
SOME OF IT MAY STILL
BE IN THE TRASH.
WHAT?
WELL, IT WAS QUITE LARGE.
I HAD TO THROW
MOST OF IT AWAY.
YOU... YOU... YOU...
YOU THREW MY SANDWICH AWAY?
MY SANDWICH?!
( voice echoing ):
I WANT THIS PART
SO MUCH, YOU KNOW.
IF I DON'T GET THIS PART
I'M NEVER GOING TO EAT
MACARONI AND CHEESE AGAIN.
NO, I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
THAT DOESN'T COUNT.
OH, COME ON, GUYS,
IT'S NOT LIKE I MOVED TO EUROPE.
I JUST MOVED ACROSS THE HALL.
AND WE WOULD HAVE YOU OVER
ALL THE TIME
IF IT WEREN'T FOR
MONICA'S ALLERGIES.
( quacks )
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I COULD NEVER LIE TO YOU.
SHE HATES YOU.
( phone ringing )
SHOULD I GET THAT?
HELLO.
UH, NO, JOEY'S
NOT HERE RIGHT NOW.
CAN I TAKE A MESSAGE?
YEAH, OKAY, SO THE AUDITION'S
BEEN MOVED FROM 5:00 TO 2:30.
OKAY, GREAT. BYE.
( gasps )
AREN'T YOU DRESSED YET?
AM I NAKED AGAIN?
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO MEET
MY PARENTS IN 15 MINUTES.
YEAH, OKAY, I WAS JUST
TALKING TO THE GUYS.
LOOK AT THEM.
I MEAN, IS IT OKAY
IF THEY COME VISIT?
WHAT ABOUT MY ALLERGIES?
OH, RIGHT.
YOUR ALLERGIES.
ALL HER. SHE HATES YOU.
OH, OH, OH,
OH, OH, OH.
YES! HA-HA-HA!
HEY, HOW COOL WOULD IT BE
IF YOU COULD WATCH, LIKE, A REAL
LIFE-SIZED VERSION OF THIS, HUH?
I MEAN, HOW CRAZY
WOULD THAT BE?
AS CRAZY AS SOCCER?
( phone ringing )
HELLO.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THE AUDITION'S NOT TILL 5:00.
WELL, NOBODY
TOLD ME.
WHO'D YOU TALK TO?
NEVER MIND.
YOU MEAN, YOU DIDN'T
GET IT FROM THIS?
THE ALLERGY GUY GOT THE PART.
THANKS.
WELL, MAYBE WE CAN
FIX IT, YOU KNOW.
MAYBE WE CAN SEND HIM SOME, SOME
BIG, BIG FLOWERS AND SCARE HIM.
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS
TO ME, CHANDLER?
THIS PART COULD HAVE TURNED
MY WHOLE CAREER AROUND.
I MESSED UP, OKAY?
I'M SORRY.
I REALLY MESSED UP.
YOU DON'T EVEN
LIVE HERE ANYMORE.
WHY ANSWER MY PHONE?
I HAVE A MACHINE.
WHICH I BOUGHT FOR YOU.
TAUGHT YOU HOW TO USE IT.
YOU THOUGHT IT WAS A COPIER.
LOOK, IF THERE WAS ANYTHING
I COULD DO, I WOULD DO IT, OKAY?
BUT EVERYBODY'S ALLOWED
ONE MISTAKE, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW, HE COULD
HAVE GOT ME A VCR
OR A SET OF GOLF CLUBS.
BUT, NO, HE HAS TO GET ME
THE WOMAN REPELLER.
THE EYESORE FROM THE LIBERACE
HOUSE OF CRAP!
NOT THAT BAD.
OH, YEAH, EASY
FOR YOU TO DAY.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO WALK AROUND
SPOTTING SOME REJECT
FROM THE MR. T COLLECTION.
CHANDLER, CHANDLER...
I PITY THE FOOL
WHO PUTS ON MY JEWELRY.
I DO! I DO!
I PITY THE FOOL
IF I...
WHEN YOU WERE LATE LAST NIGHT,
KATHY AND I GOT TO TALKING
AND... ONE THING LED TO ANOTHER,
AND...
AND WHAT?
DID YOU SLEEP WITH HER?
NO, NO, NO.
I JUST KISSED HER.
WHAT?! THAT'S EVEN WORSE!
HOW IS THAT WORSE?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT IT'S THE SAME.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I HAVE NO EXCUSES.
I WAS TOTALLY
OVER THE LINE.
OVER THE LINE?
YOU'RE SO FAR PAST THE LINE
THAT YOU CAN'T EVEN
SEE THE LINE.
THE LINE IS A DOT TO YOU.
LOOK, I'M NOT SAYING
YOU SHOULD MAGICALLY
FORGIVE ME
BUT YOU'RE NOT PERFECT.
YOU'VE MADE SOME ERRORS
IN JUDGMENT, TOO.
NAME ONE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, MAN! HE PROMISED
HE WOULDN'T TAKE THE CHAIRS.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
HOW WERE YOU LOCKED IN
AND WHERE THE HELL'S
ALL OF OUR STUFF?
WELL, THIS GUY CAME BY
TO LOOK AT THE UNIT
AND HE SAID HE DIDN'T THINK
IT WAS BIG ENOUGH
TO FIT A GROWN MAN.
SO... YOU GOT
IN VOLUNTARILY?
I WAS TRYING
TO MAKE A SALE.
OH, MAN. IF I EVER RUN
INTO THAT GUY AGAIN
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO?
BEND OVER?
THERE'S LORRAINE.
OKAY, NOW, REMEMBER--
NO TRADING.
YOU GET THE PRETTY ONE,
I GET THE MESS.
HI, JOEY.
HEY.
WELL, WELL,
LOOK WHAT YOU BROUGHT.
AND WHAT DID YOU BRING?
SHE'S CHECKING HER COAT.
JOEY, I'M GOING TO GO WASH
THE CAB SMELL OFF MY HANDS.
WILL YOU GET ME
A WHITE ZINFANDEL
AND A GLASS OF RED
FOR JANICE.
JANICE?
OH... MY... GOD.
JOEY'S TAILOR...
TOOK ADVANTAGE OF ME.
WHAT?
NO WAY.
I'VE BEEN GOING TO THE GUY
FOR 12 YEARS.
OH, COME ON. HE SAID
HE WAS GOING TO DO MY INSEAM.
THEN HE RAN HIS HAND
UP MY LEG
AND THEN,
THERE WAS DEFINITE...
WHAT?
CUPPING.
THAT'S HOW THEY DO PANTS.
ROSS, WILL YOU
TELL HIM?
ISN'T THAT HOW A TAILOR
MEASURES PANTS?
YES, YES, IT IS-- IN PRISON!
I SAID, "NAME ONE."
( door shuts )
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I DID THIS.
WHAT AN IDIOT.
OH, STOP BEATING
YOURSELF UP.
PEOPLE MAKE MISTAKES.
THESE THINGS HAPPEN.
THERE AREN'T
ANY MESSAGES
THAT YOU'VE FORGOTTEN
TO GIVE ME, ARE THERE?
WELL, APPARENTLY,
YOU'RE NOT VERY GOOD AT IT.
DO YOU THINK HE'LL
EVER FORGIVE ME?
OF COURSE HE WILL,
BUT, CHANDLER
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IS
THAT YOU FORGIVE YOURSELF.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I KIND OF HAVE.
ALREADY?
THAT WAS PRETTY BAD,
WHAT YOU DID.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
HE WILL FORGIVE YOU
AND I LIKE TO BRING
A PAD WITH ME
WHEN I GO ANSWER THE PHONE,
JUST IN CASE.
OKAY.
YOU DIDN'T SEE HOW
MAD HE WAS, YOU KNOW?
I'M SURE HE WILL FORGIVE YOU.
LOOK, WE'VE ALL BEEN THERE.
YOU KNOW, YOU FIGHT;
YOU MAKE UP--
THAT'S JUST THE WAY IT WORKS.
IT TOOK TWO PEOPLE
TO BREAK UP
THIS RELATIONSHIP.
YEAH, YOU AND THAT GIRL
FROM THE COPY PLACE
WHICH, YESTERDAY, YOU TOOK
FULL RESPONSIBILITY FOR.
I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS
TAKING RESPONSIBILITY
FOR, OKAY?
I DIDN'T FINISH
THE WHOLE LETTER.
WHAT?
I FELL ASLEEP.
YOU FELL ASLEEP?
IT WAS 5:30
IN THE MORNING
AND YOU HAD RAMBLED
ON FOR 18 PAGES.
FRONT AND BACK!
( groans )
OH-OH-OH, AND BY THE WAY
Y-O-U APOSTROPHE R-E
MEANS "YOU ARE."
Y-O-U-R MEANS "YOUR."
HA! YOU KNOW,
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I EVEN THOUGHT OF GETTING
BACK TOGETHER WITH YOU.
WE ARE SO OVER.
( choked up ):
OH... OH... OH...
FINE BY ME!
AND HEY, JUST SO YOU KNOW...
IT'S NOT THAT COMMON
IT DOESN'T HAPPEN TO EVERY GUY
AND IT IS A BIG DEAL!
I KNEW IT!
YOU HAD NO RIGHT
TO GO OUT WITH HIM.
THAT IS THE MOST
RIDICULOUS...
YOU SOLD ME OUT!
I DID NOT!
YES, YOU DID!
WOULD YOU
LET ME TALK?!
DID YOU JUST FLICK ME?
OKAY, WELL,
YOU WOULDN'T
LET ME FINISH
AND I WAS JUST...
OW! THAT HURT! OW!
OH! ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
LET'S NOT DO THIS!
( shrieking )
HAPPY THOUGHTS!
NO! NO!
Rachel:
STOP IT!
OH! OH!
NOW I'M GOING TO KICK SOME ASS!
OW!
OW! OW! OW!
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, I WILL LET GO
IF YOU BOTH STOP.
FINE.
THERE WE GO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF WE WERE IN PRISON
YOU GUYS WOULD BE,
LIKE, MY BITCHES.
OKAY, BUDDY BOY, HERE IT IS.
YOU HIDE MY CLOTHES,
I'M WEARING EVERYTHING YOU OWN.
OH, MY GOD!
LOOK AT ME!
I'M CHANDLER!
COULD I BE WEARING
ANY MORE CLOTHES?
MAYBE IF I
WASN'T GOING COMMANDO...
( choked groaning )
WHOO! I TELL YOU, IT'S HOT
WITH ALL THIS STUFF ON.
I... I BETTER NOT DO ANY,
I DON'T KNOW, LUNGES.
♪ LIVIN' ALONE ♪
♪ I THINK OF ALL THE FRIENDS
I'VE KNOWN ♪
♪ BUT WHEN I DIAL
THE TELEPHONE ♪
♪ NOBODY'S HOME ♪
♪ ALL BY MYSELF ♪
♪ DON'T WANNA LIVE ♪
♪ ANYMORE ♪
♪ ALL BY MYSELF... ♪
JOEY...
GOT YOU THE JOEY SPECIAL--
TWO PIZZAS.
JOE?
( phone ringing )
HELLO.
DAMN IT!
NO, JOEY'S NOT HERE RIGHT NOW
BUT I CAN TAKE A MESSAGE...
I THINK.
HE'S STILL GOT A CHANCE
FOR THE PART?
OH, THAT'S GREAT NEWS!
WELL, NO,
OBVIOUSLY NOT FOR THE ACTOR
WHO WAS MAULED BY HIS DOG.
OH, WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
I WILL GIVE JOEY THE MESSAGE.
THANK YOU.
YES!
OKAY... MAC AUDITION
AT 2:00...
ALLERGY ACTOR ATTACKED...
BY DOG
NOT FLOWERS.
OKAY.
HEY.
PLEASE TELL ME
YOU GOT THE MESSAGE.
WHAT MESSAGE?
THE ACTOR PLAYING MAC
COULDN'T DO IT.
THEY NEEDED TO SEE YOU AT 2:00.
WHAT?
IT'S 6:00.
( stammering ):
I WROTE IT ON THE BOARD!
I WROTE IT ON THE BOARD
AND THEN I WENT ALL
OVER NEW YORK CITY
LOOKING FOR YOU.
I WENT TO ROSS'S.
I WENT TO THE COFFEEHOUSE.
I WENT TO ANYPLACE
THAT THEY MAKE SANDWICHES.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS, CHANDLER.
I'M SORRY.
I-I-I-I DON'T
KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
WELL, Y-YOU MIGHT SAY...
"CONGRATULATIONS."
I SAW THE BOARD.
I WENT TO THE AUDITION.
I GOT THE PART!
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE FUNNY?
I WAS REALLY WORRIED OVER HERE.
OH, WELL, I'M SORRY.
SOMETIMES THAT FAKE-
OUT THING IS MEAN.
OH, WOW, OKAY, MAN, I'M SORRY.
I DID NOT MEAN
TO MAKE YOU FEEL BAD.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD...
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T...
AND I'M INCREDIBLY
HAPPY FOR YOU.
THAT'S MEAN!
YOU REALLY
HAD ME GOING THERE.
OH, WE COULD DO
THIS ALL DAY.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
OKAY, LOOK,
LET'S TALK
ABOUT WHAT A HUGE STAR
I'M GOING TO BE.
YOU ARE GOING TO
BE A HUGE STAR.
I'M GOING TO HUG YOU.
YOU HUG ME.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, DO WE DO
THIS TOO MUCH?
I THINK SO.
YEAH, GET OFF ME.
YEAH.
"COME ON, CHEESE.
"I'M NOT LEAVING
WITHOUT YOU.
"TRY ROUTING YOUR
BACKUP POWER SOURCE
THROUGH YOUR
PRIMARY C.P.U."
"I CAN'T.
"MY CIRCUITS ARE FRIED.
THEY'RE FRIED,
I TELL YOU!"
WOW.
"WELL, THEN, I'LL JUST
HAVE TO CARRY YOU."
"THAT'LL BE A NEAT
TRICK, WHEN YOU'RE...
WHEN YOU'RE DEAD!"
ROSS, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO YELL.
THERE WAS JUST AN EXPLOSION,
OKAY?
MY HEARING WOULD BE IMPAIRED.
I THOUGHT
YOU WERE EXCELLENT.
IN FACT,
FOR A MINUTE THERE
I WAS, LIKE,
"OOH, WHERE'D ROSS GO?"
THANK YOU
AND I HAVE TO SAY,
THAT FIRST SCENE
WHERE YOU MEET MAC...
OH, MY GOD.
I MEAN...
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK
THAT'S ENOUGH FOR TODAY.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]
HOLDING US BACK.
TOTALLY.